Whoo-hoo! Yeah!
Whoa! Ah!
Shman! The great rad spot
is mega-sweet for party-boarding!
Indeed.
Any calls while I was out?
Yeah.
You got a telesonic transmission
from Kif a couple hours ago.
My Kiffy called?
Kif?
Ooh, Amy, you're back!
Another hour and I would have
thought about hanging up.
Why didn't you just
leave a message, sweetie?
Well, um, I've left hundreds of messages
with your answering machine
but you never seem to get them.
Bender!
It's not my fault if you don't check me.
Messages erased.
Oh, dearest,
this long distance relationship
is too much to bear.
When even an inch separates us,
I quiver with misery.
So you can imagine how I feel
when it's a billion light-years.
Kif, don't cry,
or you'll get a tummy ache.
Lieutenant, some things came off me
and clogged the drain
so if you could... Oh-ho!
What's this?
Well, well, well.
Do my eyes believe me
or it that my bosomy swan, Leela?
Say again? You're breaking up.
Oh!
Good news, everyone!
You'll be delivering pain medicine
to the Hive Mind of Nigel 7.
Scruffy's rolling out a large pill.
You're going to Nigel 7?
Kif's on patrol near there.
You could drop me off on the way.
We could, but we won't!
It's a spaceship, damn it,
not a prom limousine.
Ooh! If anyone needs me,
I'll be in the angry dome.
This is a very long trip,
so we'll all have to go into
hibernative naptosis to save oxygen.
Aw, I don't even breathe oxygen.
Here I come, Kif.
They jumped right out of their pants.
Oh, what now?
Activate glass window.
Kif, I'm sensing a very
sensual disturbance in the force.
Prepare for ship-to-ship intimacy.
Yes, sir, Captain.
How about I help you finish that dream
you were having about me?
Okay. I was just at this part.
Oh, eh, let's try that
a little lower and a lot softer.
Imagine you stowing away
and stealing a licensed starship!
Oh, it's so romantic,
it gives me the shivers!
I don't care how much trouble I get in.
I needed to feel my lips
pressed against your lipless beak.
Oh, Amy, I can't stand having
a whole universe between us.
I've been thinking a lot about this
and, well, would you move in with me?
Here? But, uh...
Wouldn't it be crowded?
Well, no, no. It's really twice the size.
You can use the floor,
and I'll have the ceiling.
See?
Kif, you have so much
creativity and niceness,
but I'm not sure if I...
Hush. Before you answer, come thither.
This is the Holo-Shed.
It can simulate anything you desire
and nothing can hurt you,
except when it malfunctions
and the holograms become real.
Well, that probably
won't happen this time.
I wanted to show you what life
could be like if we were together.
Computer, run program "Kif One."
This is so beautiful!
Spirit!
Kif, that's the pony I always wanted
but my parents said
I had too many ponies already.
Yes, I programmed it in for you.
Four million lines of BASIC.
And... And if this isn't the life
you want, how about this?
Run program "Kif Two."
Oh, Kif!
We could live here at the shore
of the Tranquilibrius Sea in a time-share.
And I would pluck the moon from the sky
just to see you smile.
Almost got it.
It seems to be sort of stuck.
I love you!
Ooh!
Run program "Kif colon slash slash three."
This isn't bad.
My aunt had a place like this.
Amy, we could live in
a bus station bathroom for all I care.
As long as we're together,
it'll feel like a castle to me.
Kif, I'd love to live with you... Someday.
But before then, there's still lots
I want to do on my own.
What was that?
Oh, dear. I fear the Holo-Shed
might be broken again.
Well, as long as we don't
cross paths with Attila the...
Look... Spirit!
And there's Professor Moriarty.
Jack the Ripper.
Evil Lincoln.
Right-o, gents.
It's another simulation gone mad,
so murder and mayhem.
Standard procedure.
Real holographic simulated
evil Lincoln is back!
The Holo-Shed's on the fritz again.
The characters turned real!
Damn! The last time that happened,
I got slapped with three paternity suits.
- Oh, my God!
- I want Daddy!
Listen up, history's greatest villains.
Get back into the Holo-Shed
before I start blasting.
Stop!
No shoot fire stick in space canoe!
Cause explosive decompression!
Spare me your space-age
techno-babble, Attila the Hun.
Oh!
Hey!
Kif, hold on!
I totally want to!
Grab on!
- Over here!
- Please hold me. Oh, dear.
Have a good one.
Ow! Oh...
Aw, man!
Whew! After all that,
I could use some relaxation.
I'll be in the Holo-Shed.
Well, except for a few broken bones,
some internal hemorrhaging
and a partially barfed-up heart,
everyone appears fine.
Whew!
Oh, and Kif is pregnant.
Oh, joy!
Amy, isn't it wonderful?
I'm pregnant.
Yes, it's great.
A great miracle.
And not one of those bogus
everyday miracles like a sunrise.
Aren't you a male?
Yeah, what's the deal?
Just when I thought
I figured out you biological creatures,
it's something else!
Let me at him!
I'm going to take...
Look, I'm sure we're all a little unclear
on how anyone gets pregnant.
So, Kif, pray explain,
and don't spare the dirty words
where appropriate.
Well, it's quite simple, really.
When one of my species
experiences deep feelings of love,
we enter a so-called "receptive state."
You disgust me. Go on.
At that point,
our skin becomes a semi-permeable membrane
which allows the passage
of genetic material.
I held Amy's hand, and voilà.
Well, okay,
but that better be all there is.
Oh, Amy, you'll be a mother!
What a wondrous affirmation of our love
and all from the touch of your hand.
Dude, hold up.
Remember when Zapp
blew a hole in the ship?
Indeed.
Kif touched everybody there.
Couldn't any one of us be the mother?
Hey, yeah!
I mean, what about that, Kif?
Well, I suppose I might have
gotten pregnant that way,
or even from a toilet seat,
though that's impossible
since I have a private washroom.
Ah, my home away from home.
By the way, Kif, your flush seems to be
set on "stun," not "kill."
Look, Kif, I probably am the mother
although maybe I'm not.
Of course, I hope I am,
but just in case I'm not,
maybe we should have a test.
A test!
I demand a test!
Even I laughed at me
when I built this alien
cross-species genetic analyzer,
but I guess I showed myself.
Subjects, please enter the chamber.
Now to take a DNA sample.
When I pull this switch,
the maternifuge will spin at 10,000 RPM,
separating out everyone
who isn't the mother...
Father... Whatever.
Faster, faster!
Good! Fry's ejection indicates
that he is not the man-mama.
Nor is Captain Brannigan.
Oh, thank you, merciful God.
Zoidberg? What the hell
were you doing in there?
That's where I live.
I have no home.
Amy? But that means...
Leela must have impregnated me
when she grabbed my ungloved hand.
That explains the poster
in hygiene class...
"No glove, no love."
Wow, this is all so confusing.
Leela, how could you?
Our love has had to endure
your constant hatred,
and now this?
Stop testing our love!
Oh, please, Captain.
I thank Leela for the DNA she gave me,
but in my species,
the true parent is the one
who inspired the initial feeling of love.
We call that person the Smizmar,
and my Smizmar is Amy.
So the toilet seat is like
the uncle or something?
Sorry I got your boyfriend pregnant.
That's okay.
At least Kif's baby shower should be fun.
I better put it on my calendar.
Thursday, baby shower. Enter.
Might as well plan
for my new life while I'm at it.
Set motherhood mode.
To motherhood.
Mom, Dad, I know this is weird, but...
Yeah, yeah, we don't care how
squishy alien get pregnant.
All we care is that
we have grandchild now.
You're very open-minded, Mrs. Wong.
Hey, you call her Grandma now.
Call me Grandma like crazy. All the time.
Check it out, y'all.
Everyone we invited is here...
Also Zoidberg!
...so let's open the gifts!
Can't wait.
We'll start with this one from Bender.
It's my booties from when I was a kid.
Uh, they're already bronzed.
They are bronze.
And this one's from Leela.
Oh, I just love the bow.
I wonder what it is.
Yes, I wonder what we got you.
It's a basket.
For picnics?
It means a lot to me.
It's the basket my parents left me in
at the Orphanarium.
You could use it for picnics.
Here, Amy. We get this one for you.
Oh, is it a new party-board?
It's a board, all right.
An ironing board.
We had your old party-board converted
now that you not be partying anymore.
You... You trashed my party-board?
Damn right.
Now you a mom, the only surfing you do
is under a big wave of responsibility.
Oh, this is the happiest
moment of my life.
You all brought such wonderful gifts,
but the greatest gift...
Mine!
...is the bond I share
with my Smizmar Amy,
for soon, the quivering
mass of life within me
will depend upon us both.
Even now, I can sense it
feeding, squirming, searching, questing,
and shortly,
it will rend my loins in twain,
burst forth and pull us down, down, down
into the deep, dark waters of commitment.
That's so beautiful.
Yes, it's... It's...
No, I can't do this!
Oh, how could Amy leave me?
When will women learn
to take responsibility
for the children they've helped create?
The quickening! My time is near!
I must return to my homeworld
to perform the ancient birthing rites.
Let me know how that turns out.
I must now embark on a perilous journey
to give birth in precisely the same swamp
in which I was born.
If it's so dangerous,
I'd better go with you.
A gal has to protect her DNA.
No, Leela.
Tradition demands that
I make this journey with my Smizmar,
and since Amy isn't here,
I must go it alone.
Farewell, for we may never meet again.
My scrapes feel a little better now.
Hey, what's this fat, ugly thing?
A frog, a toad, or yo' mama?
It's a poisonous froad!
No one move.
I'm back, baby.
Behold...
The sacred ancestral
birthing grounds of my family.
Smells like a jockstrap.
I am the Grand Midwife!
Hi.
I am Kif of the clan Kroker,
come to bear my young.
Then let the tea of new life be brewed.
As it is writ,
"And both shall lift the jug together."
Where is your Smizmar?
She is not with me.
Oh, the sorrow!
Oh, the shame!
I'm sorry. I'm probably just
making you feel worse.
As long as Amy is with me in my heart,
I will have the strength of two.
Apparently Amy hasn't been
working out much lately.
As the tea boils,
please join hands
with your beloved Smizmar.
Oh, right.
Sorry, but I've memorized
the ceremony by rote
and it mentions her a lot.
I'll try to endure.
Good, 'cause I'm not changing it.
Now turn, ye two,
and gaze deeply into each other's eyes.
What are you looking at?
May the love I sense
between you at this moment
remain with you both
through all your days.
The tea of new life is ready.
Let those whose love created this life
speak each other's names, then drink.
Amy.
Kif!
Amy, is it you
or have I gone crazy with loneliness?
Both!
I still don't know if I'm ready for this,
but I do know I love you
and I want to be here beside you.
Great, now I lost my place.
I'm starting over.
Oh, no time.
It is begun.
Oh, my...
Ew.
Neat!
You can do it, Kif.
Ooh, nilly!
Oh, man!
Amy, my love, tell me,
are they making it to the water?
Amy!
Shoo!
Stay away from my babies!
The birthing is complete.
Oh, thank goodness.
I will now take my leave.
I live here, so I won't actually
be going anywhere,
but you don't have to talk to me anymore.
- Congratulations!
- Nice work.
Way to go, squishy!
There goes my DNA.
What a disgusting and beautiful process.
That's birth for you.
Well, we've given them a great start, Amy,
and in 20 years, they'll sprout legs
and crawl back onto land as children.
I'll be ready then.